Contact

8176923156 (Mobile) launajoy@outlook.com

www.linkedin.com/in/launawilliamson-9a654069 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Healthcare Management EMR

Certifications

RN ACLS CPR

Honors-Awards

Nursing Manager of Excellence Silver Beacon Unit - Cardiac Care Unit Quality Safety Award

Promise Cup Award
Silver Beacon Unit - Cardiac
Progressive Care Unit

Launa Williamson

Director of Patient Care Services
Grand Prairie

Summary

Proud team member of Texas Health Mansfield, which is a joint venture between Texas Health Resources and AdventHealth. Texas Health Mansfield is operated by AdventHealth and projected to open December 2020.

I am an experienced Critical Care Nurse Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Performance Improvement, Lean Six Sigma, Evidence Based Practice, Nursing Education, and Physician Relations. Strong professional with a Master's in Nursing Administration from the University of Texas at Arlington. Currently pursuing national certification in leadership.

Experience

Texas Health Mansfield Director of Patient Care Services August 2020 - Present (1 month) Mansfield, Texas, United States

Texas Health Resources
15 years 3 months
C-PCU Nurse Manager
August 2019 - August 2020 (1 year 1 month)
Fort Worth, Texas

CCU & C-PCU Nurse Manager
October 2012 - August 2019 (6 years 11 months)

CICU Day Shift Nursing Supervisor January 2010 - October 2012 (2 years 10 months) Ft. Worth, TX

RN II

June 2005 - January 2010 (4 years 8 months)

Page 1 of 2

Education

The University of Texas at Arlington

Master of Science (MS), Nursing Administration · (2015 - 2017)

The University of Texas at Arlington
Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2008 - 2010)

Tarrant County College

Associate's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2001 - 2005)